http://www.iiasa.ac.at/web/terms-of-use.html

What is IIASA
IIASA in Brief History Funding Location Goodwill Ambassador
Governance
IIASA Council Science Advisory Committee Director General/CEO Deputy Director General for Science Chief Operations Officer Management Organization Strategy
National Members
Benefits of Membership Activities with Member Countries Full List of Members Internal Council Page
Working at IIASA
Find job openings and information about careers at the institute.
Events
Regional conferences
News
Read the latest on IIASA research and activities.
Network and Alumni
News Alumni Association Research Network Distinguished Visiting Fellows Alpbach-Laxenburg Group Women in Science Club
Giving
YSSP Fund Women in Science Fund Howard Raiffa Fellows Program Peter E. de Jánosi Fellowship Ways to Give
Achievements
Highlights 2011-2015 Science and Policy Impacts Awards IIASA and the Nobel Prize
Strategy
Reducing footprints and enhancing resilience through systems analysis
Research Programs
Advanced Systems Analysis Air Quality and Greenhouse Gases Ecosystems Services and Management Energy Evolution and Ecology Risk and Resilience Transitions to New Technologies Water World Population
Large-scale Initiatives
The World in 2050 Integrated Solutions for Water, Energy, and Land Arctic Futures Initiative OECD-IIASA Partnership Tropical Futures Initiative Eurasian Economic Integration Water Futures and Solutions Global Energy Assessment
Models, Tools, and Data
View all models and tools Data Repository (DARE)
Research Projects
Read about individual research projects and activities at IIASA.
Research Partners
Read how IIASA works with research partners across the globe to deliver world-class research.
Science into Policy
Science and policy must work together to achieve a sustainable future for humanity.
Science Diplomacy
Science can help build trust between nations and support foreign policies.
Science and Art
Reaching outside the walls of science and policy.
Young Scientists Program
Application Information Online Calendar Research and Awards Alumni and Past Summers
Postdoc Opportunities
Program Representatives
Professional Benefits Guidelines for Postdocs Postdoc Fellows Testimonials
Development Partnerships
SASAC Southern African Young Scientists Summer Program
Working at IIASA
Careers at IIASA Job Openings Other opportunities
Calls for proposals
Tender invitations and freelance opportunities
Media Center
News for Journalists Nexus Blog Press Coverage Multimedia Feature Articles E-newsletter Logo guidelines
Publications
Publications Repository (PURE) Options Magazine Annual Report Policy Briefs Open Access
Models, Tools, and Data
View all models and tools Data Repository
Contacts
Find a person Keep in touch
find a person find a model or data attend an event find a publication make an inquiry find a job make a donation
About IIASA
Research
Opportunities
Resources
Contact Us
Home
Terms of use By accessing or using the IIASA website, blog, annual reports, conference sites, and other web projects associated, owned or controlled by IIASA (collectively, “IIASA Projects”) you (the “User”) agree to be bound by these terms of use (“Terms”).IIASA reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of these Terms at any time. Your continued use of IIASA Projects means that you accept and agree to the changes.These Terms affect your legal rights and obligations.If you do not agree to these Terms, do not access the IIASA Projects. About IIASAThe International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis (IIASA) was established in 1972 as a non-governmental, multi-national, autonomous scientific institution with headquarters located in Laxenburg, Lower Austria.The objectives, governance, and activities of IIASA are laid out in the institute’s Charter. The institute is subject to the laws and jurisdiction of its host country, Austria, where it is legally registered as "Verein" with registration number (ZVR-Nr) 524808900.In addition, IIASA has consultative status with the United Nations Economic and Social Council (ECOSOC).CopyrightIIASA contentIIASA content on IIASA Projects is protected by copyright, and unless otherwise stated is owned by IIASA. To ensure wide dissemination of its information, IIASA is committed to making its own content freely available and encourages the use, reproduction and dissemination of the text, multimedia and data presented. IIASA content is licensed under a
Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License. It may be translated, copied, printed and downloaded for private study, research and teaching purposes, and for use in non-commercial products or services, provided that appropriate acknowledgement of IIASA as the source is given and that IIASA's endorsement of users' views, products or services is not stated or implied in any way. Specific restrictions and/or conditions may apply to specific materials within IIASA Projects. No written permission is required for such use.IIASA also permits the incorporation of parts of its publications into other works or publications in printed, electronic, or any other media, provided these are for non-commercial research or teaching purposes and the used material is appropriately attributed to IIASA. No written permission is required for such use.However, if the materials copyrighted to IIASA are intended to be used for commercial purposes, written permission from IIASA is required.Requests for permission must be made in writing and:Clearly identify what IIASA material you would like to copy, andBriefly explain the intended use of the material.Please send all requests to permissions@iiasa.ac.at, titled “Copyright and permissions”.Non-IIASA contentIIASA Projects may include third party copyright material for which rights and permissions must be obtained from the copyright holder(s) indicated. IIASA has made every reasonable effort to locate, contact and acknowledge rights holders and to correctly apply terms and conditions to these materials. Under no circumstances shall IIASA be held responsible for any copyright infringements arising from the use of third party content.LinksIIASA Projects may contain links and references to third-party websites. The linked websites are not under the control of IIASA, and IIASA is not responsible for the content of any linked website or any link contained in a linked website. IIASA provides these links only as a convenience, and the inclusion of a link or reference does not imply the endorsement of the linked website by IIASA.Attendance at IIASA events or visiting the institute When you attend an event or conference organized by IIASA, or visit the institute, your data is processed for the purpose of effective management of the visit/event. This may include the use of your data for receiving email messages and updates regarding the event, management and distribution of reports, visit follow-up, and sharing of event related information. For the purpose of the event organization, IIASA might need to share the personal data provided with the event partners. Please note that partners in countries outside the EU may not provide the same level of data protection.Photographs, audio, and video may be captured during your visit. By attending, visitors grant IIASA permission to photograph and/or record them at the visit and distribute (both now and in the future) the attendee’s image or voice in photographs, videotapes, electronic reproductions, and audiotapes of such events and activities. Additionally, presentations, interventions, or comments made during the event may be used on the IIASA website and for further publicity in relation to the event.  IIASA is funded and governed by its National Member Organizations (NMOs). As part of our reporting to our funders we provide them with information on conference and visitors. If you need any further information or want to withdraw this consent please email .Mailing listsWhen you subscribe to receive information from IIASA, you grant your consent to the collection and use of personal data on the form for receiving information about IIASA, including general information, newsletters, publications, and events. IIASA will keep all personal data strictly confidential. We will not share your personal information with or sell it to third-party marketers. We may use the following third-party service providers (MailChimp.com) to process and store your data for the purpose above.This consent can be withdrawn any time by sending an e-mail to  or by updating your subscription preferences at www.iiasa.ac.at/subscribe.Donors IIASA collects and uses personal information such as: name, address, telephone number, and email address when a donor voluntarily provides this information. IIASA will keep all personal data strictly confidential. We will not share your personal information with or sell it to third-parties. Your information is kept on file for tax purposes and is also used in our development and communication activities.Your contact information will be used to acknowledge your donation and to notify you of development activities at IIASA. Your name will be published on IIASA owned media such as the website and annual report acknowledging your donation. If you need any further information or want to withdraw this consent please email .DisclaimerThe information, products, and services contained on IIASA Projects are provided “as is” without any warranties. The information presented does not necessarily reflect the views of IIASA staff, visitors, National Member Organizations, partner organizations, or funders.IIASA accepts no responsibility for losses, damages, costs, and other consequences resulting directly or indirectly from use of IIASA Projects and any information or material available from them. Nor does it guarantee that use of the information is free of any claims of copyright infringement.The mention of names of specific companies, products, or services on the IIASA site does not imply any endorsement or recommendation on the part of IIASA.Privacy notice and cookiesBy accessing IIASA Projects, certain information, such as Internet protocol (IP) addresses, navigation behavior through the Site, the software used and the time spent, along with other similar information, will be collected using cookies. This information is anonymous and will not specifically identify users.Cookies are widely used because they allow a website to recognize a user’s device and/or activity, therefore allowing enhanced functionality and anonymous statistics, which do not specifically identify users. Such tools are: Google Analytics, Jetpack for WordPress, AddThis, social share buttons, Disqus.If you wish to restrict or block cookies you can set your web browser to do so.The information will be used internally only for traffic analysis, statistical purposes and will not be published for general access. IIASA assumes no responsibility for the security of this information.All information collected on IIASA Projects will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold or rented to parties outside of IIASA. IIASA will use this information only for the purposes disclosed by IIASA in advance of such data collection. This document explains how we use your data while using online meeting tools.Read about your rights on the eugdpr.org resource.ForumsIIASA Projects may contain forums, comment sections, bulletin boards, chat rooms, possibility to subscribe to mailing lists or other message or communication facilities (collectively, “Forums”), the User agrees to use the Forums only to send and receive messages and materials that are proper and related to the particular Forum. By way of example and not as a limitation, the User agrees that when using a Forum, he or she shall not do any of the following:Defame, abuse, harass, stalk, threaten or otherwise violate the legal rights (such as rights of privacy and publicity) of others;Publish, post, distribute or disseminate any defamatory, infringing, obscene, indecent or unlawful material or information;Upload or attach files that contain software or other material protected by intellectual property laws (or by rights of privacy and publicity) unless the User owns or controls the rights thereto or has received all consents therefor as may be required by law;Upload or attach files that contain viruses, corrupted files or any other similar software or programs that may damage the operation of another’s computer;Delete any author attributions, legal notices or proprietary designations or labels in any file that is uploaded;Falsify the origin or source of software or other material contained in a file that is uploaded;Advertise or offer to sell any goods or services, or conduct or forward surveys, contests or chain letters, or download any file posted by another user of a Forum that the User knows, or reasonably should know, cannot be legally distributed in such manner. The User acknowledges that all Forums and discussion groups are public and not private communications. Further, the User acknowledges that chats, postings, conferences, emails and other communications by other Users are not endorsed by IIASA, and that such communications shall not be considered to have been reviewed, screened or approved by IIASA. IIASA reserves the right to remove, for any reason and without notice, any content of the Forums received from Users, including, without limitation, email and bulletin board postings.IIASA Logo
The IIASA logo should not be used without the prior consent of IIASA. Consult our guidelines on external use of IIASA branding.Legal noticeInformation according to Section 24 and 25 of the Austrian Media Act and Section 5 of Austrian E-Commerce Act (§§ 24 and 25 MedienG and § 5 ECG):Media Owner: International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis (Internationales Institut für angewandte Systemanalyse), ZVR-524808900, Schloßplatz 1, 2361 Laxenburg, AustriaPhone: (+43 2236) 807 0Email: Objectives: IIASA’s mission is to provide insights and guidance to policymakers worldwide by finding solutions to global and universal problems through applied systems analysis in order to improve human and social wellbeing and to protect the environment.   Director General: Albert van JaarsveldEditorial Policy: IIASA Projects are independent electronic mediums for scientific research and publications.
Print this page Last edited: 09 April 2020
CONTACT DETAILS
External Relations, Communications, and Library Tel: +43 2236 807 0 Fax: +43 2236 71313
IIASA, Schlossplatz 1, A-2361, Laxenburg, Austria
Subscribe to IIASA News and Publications
International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis (IIASA)
Schlossplatz 1, A-2361 Laxenburg, Austria Phone: (+43 2236) 807 0 Fax:(+43 2236) 71 313
International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis (IIASA) - Schlossplatz 1 - A-2361 Laxenburg, Austria - (+43 2236) 807 0 -
Fraud alert | Terms of use
